starmakerstudios.com 2017-06-26

# StarMaker

Starmaker Privacy Policy  
Effective: October 24, 2016 

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes the privacy practices that we, Starmaker Interactive Inc. ("Starmaker" or "We"), employ with regard to collecting, using and disclosing information, both personal and non-personal information, that we receive when you use our Services. When we say "Services" in this Privacy Policy, we mean the "Services" as defined in our Terms of Service, accessible at http://www.starmakerstudios.com/terms and via our mobile device applications. This Privacy Policy applies only to those websites, services and applications included within "Services" and doesn't apply to any third-party websites, services, or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services. By using the Services you consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE PRACTICES EXPLAINED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT ACCESS, BROWSE OR USE THE STARMAKER SERVICES.

We are committed to safeguarding any personal information collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information on our Services. We also want to inform you about your choices regarding information you share with us. If you have any questions or concerns, please let us know (see "How to contact us" section below).

Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service, accessible at www.starmakerstudios.com/terms. As used in this Privacy Policy, the terms "using" and "processing" information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

### How We Collect Info

#### We collect info in the following ways:

  * We collect information when you complete your registration to join Starmaker and access the Services and/or by logging into an account that you already have with certain third-party social networking sites ("SNS") (including, but not limited to, Facebook, Google+, and Twitter) via our Services. For example, our Services allow you to create an Account and login to the Services using your Facebook account credentials through Facebook Connect. We collect information that you voluntarily provide to become a registered User of our Services, and when you use certain aspects of our Services (e.g., entering an email address on a form to send an email from your Account.)
  * We collect voluntary information from you, as an Account holder, to add to your Account. This is completely voluntary on your part and we make every attempt possible to collect as little personally identifiable information to create these profiles.
  * When you browse or use our Services, technological tools including "Cookies" collect certain information, as explained in the following section.

### What Information We Collect and How We Use It:

#### Personal Information:

We collect personally identifiable information ("Personal Information," or "PII") directly from you when you create an Account. Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you either online or offline. Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your profile photo, stage name, audio recordings, video recordings, and email address. Additionally, if you register using a valid SNS account, we use the Personal Information you have already provided to the SNS (such as your "real" name, email address and other information you make publicly available on the SNS as well as additional information you've provided specific permission to Starmaker to access via the SNS) to create your Account on our Services; the information we collect may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS, so please consult the SNS's privacy and data practices. For example, by using Facebook Connect, you are allowing Starmaker to access the Personal Information in your Facebook account pursuant to the Facebook Terms of Use regarding your use of the Services via Facebook. If authorized by you, we may also access your profile and other information from SNS, like Facebook.

We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your "Non-Identifying Information," see below) to provide the Services to you. For example:

#### Account registration:

We create your Account for your use of the Services based upon the Personal Information you provide.

#### Communications:

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with Starmaker newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or update your "preferences" information in your Account settings. (See "Your choices regarding information," below.) As part of providing you the Services, we may need to provide you with certain notifications and communications, such as service announcements and administrative messages. These communications are considered part of the Services and your Account, which you may not be able to opt-out from receiving.

#### Customer service:

We use your Personal Information to respond to your questions and/or inquiries.

#### Audio & Video Content

As part of our Services, we collect and store the audio and video recordings that you choose to make within the Apps while signed into your Account. We do not store or collect audio or video recordings made within the Apps that are not connected with a valid, signed-in Account. When you save an audio recording on the Services, such audio recording is stored on our servers. Audio recordings that are uploaded to the Services are set to "public" by default, which means that anybody with an Account can view them. You can change your privacy settings to make an audio recording "private", in which case only other Account holders with whom you've shared a link to such audio recording will be able to access it. You can also delete an audio recording from your Account on the Services. Deleting an audio recording will prevent anyone (including you) from accessing the audio recording; however, Starmaker may retain an archived copy. 

When you save a video on the Services, this video is uploaded to a Starmaker owned channel(s) on the YouTube platform. The video is accessible via the Services through a link on your Account profile to the applicable channel on YouTube. When you save a video, by default the video is set as a "public" video both on the Services and on YouTube, which means that anybody can view it via the Services or YouTube. As an Account holder, you may make a video private on the Services, which will hide this video from other users of the Services and semi-hide the video on YouTube so that you can share links to the video on YouTube but it will not searchable on YouTube. Videos that you set to "private" through the Services can be shared with other Account holders by sharing a link with such other Account holders. Deleting a video from the Services makes such video inaccessible thereafter through the Services, and will make the video private on YouTube (such that only Starmaker will be able to access it). Videos saved to the Services may be used for public, private, or unlisted consumption on the YouTube platform at the sole discretion of Starmaker. Videos and information uploaded to YouTube will be governed by YouTube's privacy policy. Please review YouTube's privacy policy and terms of use prior to saving videos to your Account.

Again, by default, all audio and video recordings made and saved by you through the Services are available for public viewing on both the Services and the Starmaker owned channel(s) on YouTube. We strongly caution you that if you do not want video or audio recordings made via the Services to be publicly accessible, DO NOT save them to your Account.

### Non-Identifying Information

We also collect other information that you provide as part of registration, the operation, and personalization of your Account that cannot reasonably be used to identify or contact you (e.g., individual preferences) ("Non-Identifying Information"). Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be personally identified or contacted. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other Non-Identifying Information (for example, your viewing preferences).

We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Starmaker users to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Services and to analyze and understand how our Services are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

#### Log Data:

Our servers automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Services, including both Account holders and non-Account holders ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as the browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Services, pages of our Services that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Services, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Services and the Services' technical administration, to increase our Services' functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor our Services to our visitors' needs. For example, some of this information is collected so that when you visit the Services again, it will recognize you and the information could then be used to serve advertisements and other information appropriate to your interests. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the Services meet the criteria required to process their requests.

#### Cookies:

Like many online services, Starmaker uses "cookies" on our Services to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that your browser transfers to your computer. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize "persistent" cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Services. Second, we utilize "session ID" cookies to enable certain features of the Services, to better understand how you interact with the Services and to monitor aggregate usage by Starmaker Users and web traffic routing on the Services. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Services and then close your browser.

You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Services or all functionality of the Services. We may engage third-party service providers (including third-party advertisers) that may also place their own cookies on your browser. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of cookies and does not include use of cookies by such third parties.

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics' Demographics and Interest Reporting feature to collect information about use of the Site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit the Site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Site. We will not facilitate the merging of your Personal Data with non-personally identifiable information collected through Google Analytics unless we have given you notice of that merger. You may opt-out of Google Analytics tracking with the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

### Sharing of your information

#### Starmaker Audio and Video Recordings and Account Information:

When you register through the Services and submit Personal Information to create a profile, this information will represent you if you choose to share the audio and video recordings you create on the Starmaker platform. Your profile image, stage name, and the audio and video recordings that you have chosen to share, will be publicly accessible.

#### Information Shared with Third Parties:

We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information. We may also provide your Personal Information to our business partners or other third parties for the purpose of providing you with information on goods or services we believe will be of interest to you. Please see our Special Notice to California Residents below.

#### Service Providers:

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform Services-related services (e.g., maintenance services, database management, analytics and improvement of the Services features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Services are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf. 

#### Social Networking Sites:

We may share the information in your Account (including your Personal Information) with the SNSs that you have linked to your Account.

#### Facebook Connect:

You may share your recent activity on our Services back to your Facebook account. You will be prompted to decide whether or not your activity on the Services will be shared and disclosed on your Facebook service. We will not otherwise share content, videos, or other Account information to your Facebook account without your authorization.

#### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement:

Starmaker cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We can disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process including, but not limited to, subpoenas, to protect the property and rights of Starmaker or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity, or if it is required by law.

#### Business Transfers:

Starmaker may sell, divest, transfer, assign, share or otherwise engage in a transaction that involves, some or all of our assets, including any or all of the information described in this Privacy Policy, in the course of a corporate divestiture, merger, acquisition, joint venture, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or any other similar transaction or proceeding. 

### Your choices regarding information

You have several choices regarding the use of information on our Services: 

#### Your Audio:

You have control over whether to save and upload your audio recordings to the Services. We give you tools to send a link to the audio recording that resides on our Services.

#### Your Videos:

You have control over whether to save and upload a video to Youtube.com however, once you select to save a recording on the Services, you do not have a choice as to where that video resides. It will reside on a Starmaker owned channel(s) on the YouTube platform. We may give you the tools to favorite a video to your own YouTube channel and/or send a link to the video that resides on the YouTube platform.

#### Cookies:

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to accept cookies from our Services for any of the purposes described above, then you can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Consult your browser's technical information. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Services or all functionality of the Services. If you have any questions about how to disable or modify cookies, please let us know at the contact information provided below.

#### Changing or Deleting Your Information:

All Account holders may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their Account by contacting us or by editing their profile via the Services. With respect to recordings made through the Services: You can change your privacy settings to make an audio recording "private", in which case only other Account holders with whom you've shared a link to such audio recording will be able to access it. Account holders can also delete an audio recording from the Services, which will prevent anyone (including you) from accessing the audio recording; however, Starmaker may retain an archived copy on its servers. Through your privacy settings, videos saved to the Services can be made private on the Services, which will hide such videos from other users of the Services and semi-hide the video on YouTube so that you can share links to the video on YouTube but it will not searchable on YouTube. You may also delete a video from your Account on the Services, which will make such video inaccessible thereafter through the Services, and will make the video private on YouTube (such that only Starmaker will be able to access it).

### How we store and protect information

#### Information Security:

We care about the security of your information. We use commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of information collected and maintained through the Services. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us or guarantee that information on the Services may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by unauthorized persons.

#### Phishing:

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to Starmaker. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not request your credit card information, login information, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission's http://www.ftc.gov/.

#### Breach Notification:

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on the Services in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

#### International Transfer:

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Starmaker transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

### Do Not Track Disclosures

Our Services are not set up to respond to Do Not Track ("DNT") signals. We use third party service providers like Google Analytics for tracking purposes.

### Special Notice to California Residents

**California Shine the Light Law:** California residents may request a list of all third parties to which we have disclosed certain Personal Information about you for marketing purposes. You may make one request per calendar year. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for your response. You may request this information in writing by contacting us at: [appsupport@starmakerinteractive.com](mailto:appsupport@starmakerinteractive.com). Please allow up to thirty (30) days for a response.

**California Minors:** If you are a California resident under age 18 and you are unable to remove publicly-available information that you have submitted to Starmaker, you may request removal by contacting Starmaker at: [appsupport@starmakerinteractive.com](mailto:appsupport@starmakerinteractive.com). When requesting removal, you must be specific about the information you want removed and provide Starmaker with specific information, such as the URL for each page where the information is located, so that we can find it. Starmaker is not required to remove any information that: (i) federal or state law requires us or a third party to maintain; (ii) was not posted by you; (iii) Starmaker anonymizes, so that you cannot be identified; (iv) you don't follow our instructions for removing or requesting removal; or (v) you received compensation or other consideration for providing the information. REMOVAL OF YOUR INFORMATION FROM THE SERVICES DOES NOT ENSURE COMPLETE OR COMPREHENSIVE REMOVAL OF THAT INFORMATION FROM OUR SYSTEMS OR THE SYSTEMS OF OUR SERVICE PROVIDERS. Starmaker is not required to delete the information; Starmakers' obligations under California law are satisfied so long as we anonymize the information or render it invisible to other users and the public.

### Links to Other Sites

Our Services may contain links to other websites and services. Any information that you provide on or to a third-party website or service is provided directly to the owner of the website or service and is subject to that party's privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services and we're not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access.

Credit card payments, including recurring charges such as charges for subscriptions to the Service, are handled through Apple and Google, or other third party payment processors. Apple and Google will collect and may retain your credit card information in order to process your payment, including payment for your purchases of subscriptions or for any Service charges. We do not control this third party collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your information. Please review Apple's and Google's privacy policy and terms of use prior to submitting your payment information.

### Our Policy Toward Children:

Our Services are NOT directed to children under 13, and we do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. We take extra steps to ensure that users creating Accounts are 13 or older. If we learn that we have collected PII of a child under 13, we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible. We encourage parents to take precautions to assure that their household is safe and protected when creating and sharing this video content. 

### Changes

Any information that is collected is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise our Privacy Policy from time-to-time. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting a new Privacy Policy and updating the "last modified" date at the top of this page or by sending you an email or other notification, and we will indicate when such changes will become effective. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you are agreeing to be bound by the revised policy.

### How to contact us

If you have any questions about this Policy or any of the practices described herein, please contact us at: [appspuort@starmakerinteractive.com](mailto:appsupport@starmakerinteractive.com)
